Some of the common mistakes you may experience while learning how to do a frontside tailslide on a ledge is that you find it, once you ollie into the tailslide sometimes you don't lock in right and you find it you land about like this.
You can't tailslide that way at all.
You're not going to last very long on top of the ledge with your foot only there.
It's going to end up falling off.
So what you're going to want to do is to make sure you ollie high enough and land straight in the frontside tailslide and lock in the position.
This is going to get you best tailslide possible.
Another problem you may experience is a tailslide sliding out.
When you first learn how to tailslide on a ledge, you're going to find out that maybe you're trying to push it a little too hard or maybe you put too much wax on top of the ledge.
Another thing could be that you have stickers on your tail that end up making it a little too slippery.
So, if you start to slide out that just means you need to lean a little more far forward to hold your tailslide a little steadier and a little bit longer.
Another problem people experience is coming out of a frontside tailslide and riding away almost straight away like a mini ramp.
What you want to do is make sure that you can control your frontside tailslide and pop out ninety degrees and even add like a little bit of an ollie or at least come out nice and level.
You don't want your tailslide to fall out and roll away even though you could.
What you want to do is put a little tap on there and get out and roll away cleanly.